<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

        <questGiver>
            <name>Mentor</name>
            <level>
                <name>Forest</name>
                <story>The forests have always been a beautiful part of the Kingdom. Your mentor has asked for you two to meet here.</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Caves</name>
                <story>These caves were once used for mining materials used to make weapons and armor for knights such as yourself. These caves have been deserted for years, why would the mentor ask you to come down here?</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Dungeon</name>
                <story>Housing some of the most dangerous prisoners, the Dungeon is a fortress of scum. It's not your turn for guard duty, why would the mentor want to meet you here?</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Fields</name>
                <story>The fields are home to many of the peasants you protect on a daily basis. Your mentor has never taken kindly to these harsh lands, it seems odd that he would ask to meet here. Find him.</story>
            </level>
        </questGiver>

        <questGiver>
            <name>Princess</name>
            <level>
                <name>Forest</name>
                <story>The forests have always been a beautiful part of the Kingdom. The princess requested that you meet her here as soon as possible. This sounded urgent, you should find her.</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Caves</name>
                <story>These caves were once used for mining materials used to make weapons and armor for knights such as yourself. On your morning patrol you saw the Princess enter this place. You should find her before she gets hurt.</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Dungeon</name>
                <story>Housing some of the most dangerous prisoners, the Dungeon is a fortress of scum. This isn't exactly a place for a princess, why would she ask you to meet her here? You should find her.</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Fields</name>
                <story>The fields are home to many of the peasants you protect a daily basis. Perhaps the princess asked you to meet her here because she wanted to spend some time with the people. You should find her.</story>
            </level>
        </questGiver>

        <questGiver>
            <name>Seer</name>
            <level>
                <name>Forest</name>
                <story>The forests have always been a beautiful part of the Kingdom. The letter from the Seer said to meet him here. You should look for him.</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Caves</name>
                <story>These caves were once used for mining materials used to make weapons and armor for knights such as yourself. Why would the Seer want to meet down here? Oh well, walk around and find him.</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Dungeon</name>
                <story>Housing some of the most dangerous prisoners, the Dungeon is a fortress of scum. The Seer hardly leaves his village, why would he want to meet here?</story>
            </level>
            <level>
                <name>Fields</name>
                <story>The fields are home to many of the peasants you protect on a daily basis. Fitting for the Seer to ask you to meet him in his home land. You should look for him.</story>
            </level>
        </questGiver>

</resources>