<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

	<QuestGiver>
		<name>Farmer</name>
		<motive>
			<motiveName>clear rodents</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>NORMAL</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>G'day stranger! I'm sure you're aware of the rodents that have been plaguing are farms for the last couple' days; almost half my harvest has been lost to those vermin! Listen, could you help out an old farmer and rid this land of those vile creatures? I'll be sure to reward ya.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>It'll take me weeks to recover from this!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>You've done me and my family a great service, friend! I don't got much, but please choose a reward from my box o' loot.</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bat</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Rat</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Albino</enemyName>
			</enemy>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>lost tools</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>NORMAL</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>Now where did I lose those tools? Oh, hi there stranger! Listen, you wouldn't happen to be lookin' for some work would ya? See, I seem to have misplaced my box o' tools somewhere around these parts. If you were to find 'em for me I'd really appreciate it. I'd even give ya a reward from my box o' loot!</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>I sure do appreciate you're help!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>You found 'em! I can't tell you how grateful I am, friend! Now I promised you a reward from my box o' loot, and I aim to deliver! Please, choose somethin'.</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>
			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bat</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Crab</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Albino</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>Tools</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>missing heirloom</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>SERIOUS</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>Still lookin' for work, huh? Been there, friend! Well, now that you mention it, our farm was recently raided by some bandits; now I'm no stranger to bein' robbed, these are dangerous times we live in after all, and I would've paid no mind to it had they not stolen one of my most prized possessions - a family heirloom that has been passed down for generations. If you can retrieve that heirloom from them hoodlums, I'd be eternally grateful, friend!</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>That heirloom ain't even worth much, why would they take it?</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>My heirloom! Friend, words can't express my gratitude, so maybe some coin and a reward from my box o' loot can!</questCompleteDialogue>

			<actTwoOpeningStory>After retrieving the farmer's heirloom, he invited you in for a cooked meal and even allowed you to stay in his barn. You were in no position to turn down food and a bed, so naturally, you took the farmer up on his offer. A few days later, you received a letter from your new farmer-friend asking for your help yet again. You better find him.</actTwoOpeningStory>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bandit</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Thief</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>Heirloom</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>hunting</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>SERIOUS</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>You're lookin' for more work huh? I won't turn down a helpin' hand that's for sure! You seem like a feller that can handle himself, so I've got just the task for you! I'm runnin' low on my supplies of meat, and I ain't had the time to go huntin' since I've been too preoccupied with getting these here crops to grow! I need you to go huntin' for some fresh meat for me.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>Gettin' crops to grow in this draught is dang near impossible!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>I knew you wouldn't disappoint, friend! I've never been one to short change a man for a hard days work, so please, take somethin' from my box o' loot! .</questCompleteDialogue>

			<actTwoOpeningStory>After the hunt, you continued to assist the farmer with his daily chores - you weren't in any position to turn down the coin. After a few days of hard labour, the farmer had no work to give you and thus, you continued on with your journey for food and coin. Recently, you received a letter from the farmer requesting your assistance yet again. You should find him.</actTwoOpeningStory>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Albino</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bat</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>ChargrilledMeat</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>destroyed farm</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>CATASTROPHE</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>Boy am I glad to see you, friend! I just can't seem to catch break. Last night a group of bandits rode through here and destroyed my farm! This ain't like the usual gang-activity we get around these parts, I mean sure, now and again a few crops'll get stolen, but never would they go so far as to actually destroy a persons property! But that's neither here nor there. Friend, I need your help again. I need to start rebuildin' right away, but I'm gonna need the right tool for the job. That's where you come in.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>I sure am glad you came as soon as you did!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>With this tool I'll have this farm up and runnin' again in no time!</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>
			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Brute</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Golem</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Shaman</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>Pickaxe</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>stolen tools</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>CATASTROPHE</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>Dang hoodlums! Why can't they earn an honest livin' instead of stealing what I worked so hard for? Sorry, friend, I ain't in the best of moods. You see, last night a group of bandits stole my dang tools! Without them, I can't work, and if I can't work, well then say goodbye to this here farm! I know you've helped me so much already, but could you track down those bandits and get my tools back? As always, there's a reward waitin' for ya.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>Gangs have been more active than ever this year!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>I can't tell you how grateful I am, friend. With these tools I can at least start makin' some ends-meet again!</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bandit</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Thief</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>Pickaxe</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>find information</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>INVESTIGATE</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>With the way things are goin' around here, it's just a matter of time before gangs overrun this place! Hmm, maybe Terry knows what's goin' on. Who's Terry you ask? She's helped me a lot over the years when it comes to getting information, the girl knows just about everything! Listen, could you go ask her if she knows what's got these gangs so riled up lately? I'd do it myself but I've got a lot of work to do here on the farm.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>I sure do hope Terry can help us out with this one!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>The farmer sent ya? Yeah I think I know what's goin' on. You see, with the recent passin' of the captain of the Knights Guard, the Kingdom has been preoccupied with choosin' his successor, so much so that they ain't been out on patrol in weeks. Because of all this, gangs all over the place have decided that now's their time to take just about as much as they can without fear of the Knights Guard catchin' 'em. That's about as much as I know, stranger.</questCompleteDialogue>

			<actThreeOpeningStory>After listening to everything Terry had to say, you rushed back to the farmer to tell him the news. At first, he seemed distraught, but a few moments later, there was a spark in his eye - an idea, perhaps? He told you to meet him back here in a few days. Now that it's been a few days, you should find him.</actThreeOpeningStory>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>speak</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<npc>
				<npcName>Terry</npcName>
			</npc>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>take out gang members</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>INVESTIGATE</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>I can't sit idly by and let this here land be overrun by them hoodlums! We need to find out what's got 'em so riled up! These bandits must have some sorta secret document on 'em that will shed some light onto what's been goin' on. As you know, I'm not one for fightin', but if you do this for me, as always, there's a reward waitin' for ya.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>We'll show those hoodlums!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>Ahh so that's what's goin' on! How're we gonna solve that?</questCompleteDialogue>

			<actThreeOpeningStory>The letter that you found reads: 'Keep terrorizing the land's citizens until they hand over all their earthly possessions to us! The Knights Guard is sure to choose a new captain soon, so we won't be able to do this for much longer! - your leader'. It seems that the Knights Guard have been too preoccupied to protect us lately. The farmer has told you that he has an idea. You should find him.</actThreeOpeningStory>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bandit</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Thief</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>Letter</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>special seeds</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>STRENGTHEN</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>Before we take the fight to those hoodlums, I gotta ask another favour of ya, friend. See, I can't risk any more of my crops bein' destroyed by them bandits, so I've got no choice but to turn to magic! Legend tells of creatures that possess powerful seeds; seeds that produce dang near indestructible crops! If you could find me just one of those magic seeds, we'd be set for life!</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>Never saw myself as a 'magic seeds' kinda farmer, but times're tough, friend!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>You found 'em? I'M GONNA BE SO RI...I mean WE'RE gonna be so rich!</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Succubus</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Monk</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>SpecialSeeds</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>new captain</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>STRENGTHEN</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>I suppose I should tell you the truth, friend. Before becomin' a measily farmer, I was once part of the Knights Guard. Heck, I was one of the best Knights that they had ever seen. Why am I tellin' you this? Well, I happen to know that when they choose the Captain of the Knights Guard, they don't care about what background you came from, just as long as you can deliver! In all my years, I ain't never seen a warrior as skilled as you, I believe you've got what it takes. Bring me a trophy from a powerful enemy, and I'll convince the Knights Guard to make you their captain. Yep, just like that, no strings attached.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>I sure do miss my heroic days as a Knight.</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>Now THIS is a trophy! Welcome to the Knights Guard, Captain!</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill_fetch</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Eye</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Monk</enemyName>
			</enemy>

			<item>
				<itemName>DriedRose</itemName>
			</item>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>kill boss</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>RESOLVE</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>Now we're ready to take this fight to the leader himself! Kill the gang leader and give this land back to the people it belongs to!</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>Will sure be nice to not have to worry about hoodlums rummaging through my belongings!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>Thanks to you, we all sleep soundly once again! I'm proud to call you my friend.</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>kill</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Bandit</enemyName>
			</enemy>
			<enemy>
				<enemyName>Thug</enemyName>
			</enemy>

		</motive>

		<motive>
			<motiveName>diplomacy</motiveName>
			<storyPhase>RESOLVE</storyPhase>

			<questNotGivenDialogue>In all my years, I ain't never come across a feller that was so good with words. I believe we can end this plight without any more bloodshed. I've heard that the leader of the gangs is one for deals, so why don't ya try and convince him to leave these lands and it's people alone? Of course, if ya'll can't come to an agreement, you know what to do.</questNotGivenDialogue>
			<questGivenDialogue>You've got the voice of the people on your side, friend!</questGivenDialogue>
			<questCompleteDialogue>You make a compelling argument, peasant. Very well, we will leave this land and seek other forms of income. You and the people are safe, you have my word.</questCompleteDialogue>

			<objectiveType>
				<objectiveTypeName>speak</objectiveTypeName>
			</objectiveType>

			<npc>
				<npcName>GangLeader</npcName>
			</npc>

		</motive>

	</QuestGiver>
</resources>
